{
    "subject": "Duke_Karl-Theodor_in_Bavaria",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Princess_Sophie_of_Saxony",
    "human_readable": "Duke Karl-Theodor in Bavaria is married to Princess Sophie of Saxony.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9782924056053162,
            "question": "Who is Duke Karl-Theodor in Bavaria married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9478541612625122,
            "question": "Who is Duke Karl-Theodor in Bavaria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9295464158058167,
            "question": "Is there a relationship between Duke Karl-Theodor and Princess Sophie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9179590344429016,
            "question": "Is Princess Sophie of Saxony married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8830612897872925,
            "question": "Where is Duke Karl-Theodor in Bavaria from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7535960674285889,
            "question": "What title does Duke Karl-Theodor in Bavaria hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6409019231796265,
            "question": "What is the name of Princess Sophie's husband's duchy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6257665157318115,
            "question": "Which country does Princess Sophie of Saxony represent?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6213534474372864,
            "question": "What is the name of Princess Sophie's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.528160810470581,
            "question": "To which royal family does Princess Sophie belong?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Duke Karl-Theodor in Bavaria is married to Princess Sophie of Saxony.",
            "html": "yago_31072_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Princess Sophie's husband?",
            "html": "yago_31072_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which country does Princess Sophie of Saxony represent?",
            "html": "yago_31072_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Princess Sophie's husband's duchy?",
            "html": "yago_31072_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31072_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31072_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31072_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31072_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31072_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31072_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31072_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31072_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31072_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31072_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can confirm that the triple \"Duke Karl-Theodor in Bavaria is married to Princess Sophie of Saxony\" is indeed supported by the documents.\n\nHere's the JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe multiple documents mention the marriage between Duke Karl-Theodor in Bavaria and Princess Sophie, confirming that they are indeed spouses."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that Duke Karl-Theodor in Bavaria was married to Princess Sophie of Saxony. Specifically, document `37.txt` and `119.txt` mention their marriage on 11 February 1865."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}